=Deity Of Love= =Episode 7=
= إله الحب = = الحلقة 7 =
If you want to refine the pill,
إذا كنت تريد تحسين حبوب منع الحمل ،
it is necessary to be familiar with
من الضروري أن تكون على دراية
all kinds of herbs.
جميع أنواع الأعشاب.
So many herbs here!
الكثير من الأعشاب هنا!
Is this Solanum nigrum or Hsuehchien?
هل هذا Solanum nigrum أو Hsuehchien؟
See,
نرى،
the one with the yellow bottom and white heart
الواحد ذو القاع الأصفر والقلب الأبيض
is Solanum nigrum.
هو Solanum nigra.
Solanum nigrum.
Solanum nigra
You made it?
لقد فعلتها؟
Yes.
نعم.
It looks good
إن شكلها جيد
on you.
عليك.
It's going to rain.
ستمطر.
Let's go down the mountain.
لننزل الجبل.
Okay.
تمام.
It is likely to rain for a whole day.
من المحتمل أن تمطر ليوم كامل.
How did you know it's raining?
كيف علمت أنها تمطر؟
By instinct.
بالفطرة.
Maybe I knew it before.
ربما كنت أعرف ذلك من قبل.
I will help you recover your memory.
سوف أساعدك على استعادة ذاكرتك.
Why do you want to know
لماذا تريد أن تعرف
the information of this jade so badly?
المعلومات من هذا اليشم بشدة؟
I haven't seen my parents since I was a kid.
لم أر والديّ منذ أن كنت طفلاً.
This jade was with me
كان هذا اليشم معي
when my master brought me back.
عندما أعادني سيدي.
When
متي
my memory recovers,
ذاكرتي تتعافى ،
I'll help you find your parents.
سأساعدك في العثور على والديك.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
(Usage of Talisman is a required course for Demon Hunters.)
(استخدام التعويذات هو دورة مطلوبة لصيادي الشياطين.)
(Swordsmanship is also the most important skill.)
(تعتبر مهارة المبارزة أيضًا من أهم المهارات.)
Don't you need to have a rest?
لا تحتاج للراحة؟
No,
رقم،
I'm not tired at all.
أنا لست متعبًا على الإطلاق.
Not to mention the next tryout is around the corner.
ناهيك عن أن التجربة التالية قاب قوسين أو أدنى.
Well.
نحن سوف.
(We must seize the time to practice.)
(يجب أن ننتهز الوقت للممارسة).
Wait for me.
الانتظار لي.
I'll be back soon.
سأعود قريبا.
(She is with Xiuning every day.)
(هي مع Xiuning كل يوم.)
(I'm gonna kill you.)
(سوف أقتلك.)
Xiuning.
شيونينغ.
You again.
انت مرة اخرى.
This is Qingyun Valley, our turf.
هذا هو وادي تشينغيون ، أرضنا.
Why can't I come?
لماذا لا استطيع المجيء؟
What do you want to do here?
ماذا تريد ان تفعل هنا؟
You will never pick up what we learn
لن تلتقط ما تعلمناه
in Qingyun Valley with your stupid brain.
في وادي تشينغيون مع عقلك الغبي.
You are a fool.
أنت أبله.
Stay away from me.
ابق بعيد عني.
Don't regard my goodwill as malice.
لا تنظر إلى حسن نيتنا على أنها خبث.
There will be a time when you have to beg me.
سيكون هناك وقت يتعين عليك فيه أن تتوسل إلي.
Hum.
همم.
Wan Ying,
وان ينغ ،
why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
I,
أنا،
I'm here to ask you about
أنا هنا لأسألك عن ذلك
the spiritual spell cultivation.
زراعة التعويذة الروحية.
Go to the second floor of the Library,
اذهب إلى الطابق الثاني من المكتبة ،
and read the sixth book.
ويقرأ الكتاب السادس.
But I can't understand it.
لكن لا يمكنني فهم ذلك.
Since you have read so many books, please teach me.
بما أنك قرأت الكثير من الكتب ، من فضلك علمني.
Xiaoqing.
شياو تشينغ.
Ah!
آه!
Oh, my!
أوه ، يا!
My ankle sprained.
التواء كاحلي.
Brother Xiuning,
الأخ Xiuning ،
please help me.
الرجاء مساعدتي.
Why are you holding my brother's leg?
لماذا تمسك بساق أخي؟
I sprained my foot.
لقد لويت قدمي.
Xiaoqing?
شياو تشينغ؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Why didn't you hurt?
لماذا لم تتأذى؟
You want me to get hurt?
تريدني أن أتأذى؟
It is you that
هذا هو أنت
make the Pill Room explode.
اجعل غرفة حبوب منع الحمل تنفجر.
You're talking nonsense!
أنت تتحدث عن هراء!
You can't accuse me of it without evidence
لا يمكنك أن تتهمني بذلك بدون دليل
because Xiuning likes you.
لأن Xiuning تحبك.
What are you doing? Let me go!
ماذا تفعل؟  دعني اذهب!
You said it wasn't you.
قلت أنه ليس أنت.
Xiaoqing,
شياو تشينغ ،
are you all right?
هل انت بخير؟
Brother,
أخ،
I was framed by her.
لقد تم تأطري بها.
Did you make the Pill Room explode?
هل جعلت غرفة حبوب منع الحمل تنفجر؟
It's not me.
ليس انا.
(The Chief is here.)
(الرئيس هنا.)
The Chief?
الرئيس؟
My Lord, are there any things
ربي هل هناك شيء
you want us to do?
تريد منا أن نفعل؟
I'm here to
أنا هنا من أجل
find the demon
ابحث عن الشيطان
because Qingyun Valley is filled with
لأن وادي تشينغيون مليء
the breath of a demon not long ago.
نفس الشيطان منذ وقت ليس ببعيد.
We should keep away from the demon,
يجب أن نبتعد عن الشيطان ،
in case the demon hurts us.
في حال جرحنا الشيطان.
A demon with us?
شيطان معنا؟
It's impossible.
هذا مستحيل.
People in the valley are all acquaintances.
الناس في الوادي كلهم ​​معارف.
The appearance of the demon can change,
يمكن أن يتغير مظهر الشيطان ،
so it's hard to tell.
لذلك من الصعب معرفة ذلك.
This means that everyone is suspicious.
هذا يعني أن الجميع مشبوهون.
It's her.
إنها هي.
It must be her.
يجب أن تكون هي.
She's the newcomer.
إنها الوافدة الجديدة.
She must be the demon.
يجب أن تكون الشيطان.
(The right to rebroadcast the play on the Internet belongs to me.) (Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co., Ltd.)
(حق إعادة بث المسرحية على الإنترنت ملك لي.) (شركة Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co.، Ltd.)